Three girls making a killing.
The Squad is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Rick Walker.
Three gun-toting, quick-witted girls move their drug
operation to a new spring break hot spot every year.
With sales reaching $1 million, they land on the radar of a seldom seen drug lord only
known as "Frosty The Snowman" who sends his hitmen to eliminate them.
Bella, played by Alea Hansinger.
Gina, played by Meghan Carrasquillo.
Dani, played by Grace Evans.
J.C., played by Julia Avila.
The Housekeeper, played by Wil Wilson.
Taylor, played by Hannah Hunt.
Kannur Squad is a 2023 Indian Malayalam-language action thriller film directed by Roby Varghese Raj in his directorial
debut, written by Muhammed Shafi and Rony David Raj, and produced by Mammootty under Mammootty Kampany.
The film stars Mammootty, Azees Nedumangad, Rony David Raj,
Shabareesh Varma, Kishore, and Vijayaraghavan.
It is based on the real story of a team of police officers who were part of the
Kannur Squad, a crime investigation unit, formed by former Kannur SP S.
Sreejith IPS.
The film was officially announced in January 2023 under the tentative title Megastar 421,
with the title announced by Mammootty on 11 February 2023 as Kannur Squad.
Principal photography began on 27 December 2022, with filming taking place in Kannur, Kasaragod, Wayanad, Ernakulam, Athirapilly,
Thiruvananthapuram, Pala, Wai, Pune, Mumbai, Uttar Pradesh, Rajasthan, Belgaum, Mangalore and Coimbatore, concluding on 6 April 2023 in Wayanad.
The film's music is composed by Sushin Shyam, while the cinematography and
editing are handled by Muhammed Rahil and Praveen Prabhakar.
Kannur Squad was released on 28 September 2023 and received critical acclaim from critics with
praise for its cast performances, direction, script, cinematography and musical score.
The film was a major commercial success and earned ₹100 crore worldwide, emerging to become one of the
highest-grossing Malayalam film of all time and the fourth highest-grossing Malayalam film of 2023.
The tone is intense.